{
    "quizId": "111111",
    "quizTitle": "MyQuiz",
    "quizDomain": {
        "domainId": 118,
        "domain": "MEAN Stack"
    },
    "quizDuration": "661",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionId": "1",
            "question": "Which of the following is true about fork method of child_process module?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "Both of the above.",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "The fork method is a special case of the spawn to create Node processes.",
            "option2": "The fork method returns object with a built-in communication channel in addition to having all the methods in a normal ChildProcess instance.",
            "option3": "Both of the above.",
            "option4": "None of the above."
        },
        {
            "questionId": "662",
            "question": "What is applicable for dependency injection in Angular?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "All of these",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Angular ships with its own dependency injection framework",
            "option2": "You don't have to create an Angular injector",
            "option3": "Angular creates an application-wide injector for you during the bootstrap process",
            "option4": "All of these"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "663",
            "question": "If you provide a custom service in two components’ “providers” section of @Component decorator, how many instances of service shall get created?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "2",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "1",
            "option2": "2",
            "option3": "4",
            "option4": "3"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "664",
            "question": "What is not a benefit of dependency injection in Angular?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "None of these",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "easier testability",
            "option2": "better code organization",
            "option3": "better code modularization",
            "option4": "None of these"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "665",
            "question": "On the opposite side of event bindings (()) lie Angular's square-bracket syntax ([]) which signify a ____________.",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "property binding and class binding",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "property binding",
            "option2": "class binding",
            "option3": "style binding",
            "option4": "property binding and class binding"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "666",
            "question": "In Angular, you can pass data from parent component to child component using...",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "@Input()",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "@Output()",
            "option2": "@Input()",
            "option3": "Output",
            "option4": "Input"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "667",
            "question": "Which option of npm command lists, the npm version?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "-v",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "-v",
            "option2": "-version",
            "option3": "-ver",
            "option4": "None of these."
        },
        {
            "questionId": "668",
            "question": "Which character in Angular, is used to enclose for event binding?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "(",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "{",
            "option2": "(",
            "option3": "[(",
            "option4": "["
        },
        {
            "questionId": "669",
            "question": "What is the default file encoding used by fs.writeFile() method of Node.js ?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "UTF-8",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "US-ASCII",
            "option2": "UTF-8",
            "option3": "UTF-16",
            "option4": "UTF-32"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "670",
            "question": "package.json is used to ________________.",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "define the properties of a package",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "install web applications",
            "option2": "define the properties of a package",
            "option3": "install local modules",
            "option4": "define the properties of sample database."
        },
        {
            "questionId": "671",
            "question": "What is the advantage of the component-based architecture?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "Reusability",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Reusability",
            "option2": "component-based UI Approach Accelerate Development Speed",
            "option3": "It Provide Consistent User Experience throughout the Application",
            "option4": "All of these."
        },
        {
            "questionId": "672",
            "question": "Where does the ExpressJS is placed in MEAN stack?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "backend component",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "backend component",
            "option2": "frontend framework",
            "option3": "middle processing pipeline",
            "option4": "None of these"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "673",
            "question": "Which type of web application are more suitable for Angular?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "CURD applications",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Online gaming",
            "option2": "Online IDE",
            "option3": "CURD applications",
            "option4": "Depends upon the requirement"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "674",
            "question": "Choose the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of the following HTML code.",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "document.getElementById (“letsfindcourse”).innerHTML = ”I am a full stack developer”;",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "document.getElement (“letsfindcourse”).innerHTML = ”I am a full stack developer”;",
            "option2": "document.getElementById (“letsfindcourse”).innerHTML = ”I am a full stack developer”;",
            "option3": "document.getId (“letsfindcourse”) = ”I am a full stack developer”;",
            "option4": "document.getElementById (“letsfindcourse”).innerHTML = I am a full stack developer;"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "675",
            "question": "What can we attach to DOM elements in order to respond to events in the system?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "Event Listeners",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Event Handlers",
            "option2": "Event Listeners",
            "option3": "Event Processors",
            "option4": "Event Coordinators"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "676",
            "question": "Why a Node.JS code is pretty fast although being written in JavaScript?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "Being built on Google Chrome's V8 JavaScript Engine",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Node.JS internally converts JavaScript code to Java based code and then execute the same",
            "option2": "Node.JS internally converts JavaScript code to C based code and then execute the same",
            "option3": "Being built on Google Chrome's V8 JavaScript Engine",
            "option4": "None of the above"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "677",
            "question": "Why does Node not block while waiting for operations to complete?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "Asynchronous",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Static",
            "option2": "Asynchronous",
            "option3": "Synchronous",
            "option4": "Recursive"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "678",
            "question": "What is the native functions to run code asynchronously in JavaScript ?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "setTimeout",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "timeout",
            "option2": "setTimeout",
            "option3": "repeat",
            "option4": "interval"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "679",
            "question": "Which of the following statement is correct about AJAX?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "All of them",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "AJAX is based on some internet standards.",
            "option2": "All of them",
            "option3": "It is used for creating fast & dynamic webpages",
            "option4": "It is used for dynamically updating the parts of the webpage without reloading the webpage."
        },
        {
            "questionId": "680",
            "question": "JSON stands for ________________",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "JavaScript Object Notation",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Java Standard Output Network",
            "option2": "JavaScript Object Notation",
            "option3": "JavaScript Output Name",
            "option4": "Java Source Open Network"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "681",
            "question": "What method do we use to create an event listener?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "element.addEventListener()",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "element.makeEventListener()",
            "option2": "element.listen()",
            "option3": "element.on()",
            "option4": "element.addEventListener()"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "682",
            "question": "Which of the following methods are being used to send a request to the server?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "open()",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "open() & connect ()",
            "option2": "open()",
            "option3": "None of them",
            "option4": "open() & established()"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "683",
            "question": "Which of the following is not a type of JSON?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "date",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "date",
            "option2": "Object",
            "option3": "Array",
            "option4": "String"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "684",
            "question": "What is not an Angular feature, with respect to bulid a CURD app in a cohesive set?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "None of these.",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "Data-binding",
            "option2": "basic templating directives",
            "option3": "form validation",
            "option4": "None of these."
        },
        {
            "questionId": "685",
            "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax for creating an XMLHttpRequest Object?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "var xhr=new XMLHttpRequest();",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "xhr=new XMLHttpRequest();",
            "option2": "var xhr=new XMLHttpRequest();",
            "option3": "var xhr = XMLHttpRequest();",
            "option4": "None of them."
        },
        {
            "questionId": "686",
            "question": "By using AJAX, web application can send",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "Asynchronously",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "All of these",
            "option2": "As a stream",
            "option3": "Synchronously",
            "option4": "Asynchronously"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "687",
            "question": "What property on the event object contains the DOM object that invoked the event?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "event.target",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "event.element",
            "option2": "event.source",
            "option3": "event.target",
            "option4": "event.invoker"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "688",
            "question": "In AJAX, _______ ready states are available.",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "4",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "6",
            "option2": "5",
            "option3": "4",
            "option4": "8"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "689",
            "question": "What are the parameters of the method JSON.parse()?",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "both text and reviver",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "text",
            "option2": "reviver",
            "option3": "both text and reviver",
            "option4": "object"
        },
        {
            "questionId": "690",
            "question": "Observe the following JavaScript code-var text = 'Hello world !'; What is the value of text.substring(1,4)",
            "difficulty": "MED",
            "correctOption": "ell",
            "domain": {
                "domainId": 118,
                "domain": "MEAN Stack"
            },
            "option1": "ello",
            "option2": "Hell",
            "option3": "ell",
            "option4": "Hello"
        }
    ]
}